

Kartik Vaghani

MOBILE APP DEVELOPER

CONTACT



+91 8347706769



kartikpatel868@gmail.com



11, avadh bungalows, capital farm road, Mota Varachha, Surat, Gujarat 394105



in https://www.linkedin.com/in/kartikm-vaghani-1489b4aa/

EDUCATION

MKBU Bhavnagar University

Master of Science with Information Technology(M.SC.it), 2016-18

MKBU Bhavnagar University

Bachelors of Computer Application(BCA), 2011-15

Tapovan Shaikshanik Sankul(Bhavnagar)

12 Commerce in GSHSEB Board

ABOUT ME

I have 3 years of experience in Mobile Application Development. Using Android as well as Flutter and able to work in Team in an innovative and challenging environment. Desire to be a part of your corporation and provide my knowledge and skills to escort your corporation up-to-the pinnacle of success.

PERSONAL INFORMATION

Vaghani Kartik M. Name: Date of Birth: 06 August 1994

Permanent Address: 1, Rameshwar Park, B/H Shree Shitla Maa

Temple, Chitra-Sidsar road, Chitra, Bhavnagar

364004.

Marital Status: Married

Play Volleyball, Listening to Music Hobbies:

Languages Know: Gujarati, Hindi, English

WORK EXPERIENCE

• The Easy Learn Academy- Bhavnagar (Aug-2019 to Feb-2020)

I got Training in an Android Application Development From Aug 2019 to Feb 2020 in The Easy Learn Academy Bhavnagar as a Student.

• Vision infotech - surat (Dec-2020 to Feb-2022)

I Start Working in Mobile Application Development From Dec 2020 to Feb 2022 in Vision Infotech Surat as a Mobile Application Developer using **Android** as well as **Flutter**.

Some of my work references:

- https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=com.editgallerycameraphoto.motioneditphoto
- https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=com.brandever.postermaker
- https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=com.shivringtones.ganesh.shivringtones
- https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=com.movenpick.photomotion
- Rain infotech surat (March-2022 to Till Date)

I Switch my job to Flutter Application Development From Mar 2022 to Till Date in Rain Infotech Surat as a Flutter Application Developer.

Some of my work references:

- https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=io.stakingpool.cryptoshare
- https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=com.oduwa
- https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=com.oduwamultiwallet
- https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=com.offensedecentralized.android
- https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=com.rain.thoughtoftheday

OTHER EXPERIENCE

Oscar Career Point (Aug-2021 to Till Date)

I Start working as Faculty to Teach Android and Flutter Application Development From Aug 2021 to Till date in Oscar Career Point.

Red & White Multimedia Education (Jan-2023 to Till Date)

I Start working as Faculty to Teach Flutter Application Development From Jan 2023 to Till date in Red & White Multimedia Education.